bubbl.us 2015-04-30

# Bubbl.us Help

At LKCollab, LLC ("bubbl.us", "we", or "us") we respect the privacy of your information. By using bubbl.us (the "Site"), or the services provided through the Site, we may collect information about you, and use and disclose such information, as described in this privacy policy. Our Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us, and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our Site. 

### The Information We Collect

We collect Personal Information and Anonymous Information about you. 

Personal Information is information you knowingly provide to us. When you create an account on bubbl.us, you are asked to provide us with a username, email, password and your name (optional). This information is sent over a secure SSL connection. All of this data, except for your password (which is stored in encrypted form), is stored in our databases. No third party has access to this information directly or indirectly. 

Anonymous Information is information collected via technology that is not linked to Personal Information and does not enable contact with any identifiable person. As you use the Site or services, certain Anonymous Information may also be passively collected and stored, such as your Internet protocol address, browser type, and access times. We may also use Cookies (as defined below) and navigational data like Uniform Resource Locators (URLs) to gather information regarding the date and time of your visit. "Cookies" are small pieces of information that a website sends to your browser while you are viewing a website. We may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your browser until you delete them) to improve your experience on the Site (e.g., by keeping you logged in). Persistent Cookies can be removed by following your Internet browser help file directions. If you choose to disable Cookies, you may be logged out of certain portions of the Site. 

### The Ways We Use Information

We use Personal Information that you submit to us to administer your account, control access to the Site, communicate with you (i.e., send account related notifications), respond to your requests (i.e.,change or reset of username and/or password), and improve the quality of the Site and services. 

Other bubbl.us users may be able to add you to their contacts by searching for your name or email. Your email address is never shown to them in full. 

We may also use your Personal Information to create Anonymous Information records by excluding information (such as your name or email address) that makes the information personally identifiable to you. We may use these records, and other Anonymous Information, to analyze usage patterns so that we may enhance the Site or services. 

### The Ways We Disclose Information

Your saved mind maps are stored in our databases and transmitted to you via SSL encrypted connection. Any third party that may intercept such traffic will not be able to read it. It is however your responsibility to keep your account and your data secure. bubbl.us will not be held liable (see our Terms Of Service) for any data corruption that may occur. 

### Billing Information

We use the services of Stripe.com to process your payments. We do not store any of your billing information on our servers. All information is encrypted and passed directly to Stripe using a secure HTTPS connection. Stripe has been audited by a PCI-certified auditor, and is certified to PCI Service Provider Level 1. This is the most stringent level of certification available. 

### How You Can Update, Correct or Delete Your Information

You may update your username or password by emailing us at support@bubbl.us from your email address on record, or if you are a Registered User, by editing your profile (Account -> Update my information). 

If you wish to have your Personal Information removed from our databases, you may contact us at support@bubbl.us from your email address on record and let us know what Personal Information you want deleted. You may request deletion of your Personal Information by us, but please note that we may be required (by law or otherwise) to keep this information and not delete it (or to keep this information for a certain time, in which case we will comply with your deletion request only after we have fulfilled such requirements). When we delete Personal Information, it will be deleted from the active database, but may remain in our archives. 

### Changes to Our Policy

This Privacy Policy is subject to revision from time to time. We will post any revised version of the Privacy Policy on this Site. If we make any material changes to it, we will also send you an e-mail to the last e-mail address you provided to us (if any). Any amended Privacy Policy will be effective as of the date stated in the revised policy. 

### Contact us

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at support@bubbl.us
